Guide to the Yale University Films Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University Films records
1970-1989
RU 760
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
97.5
(34 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, subject files, project files, budgets and financial statements, motion picture film, videotapes, and audiotapes documenting projects and operations of Yale University Films. Records concerning the Yale Media Design Studio are also included.
Yale University. Films
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 37 (YRG 37), Records of associations, institutes, centers, and organizations affiliated with Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, subject files, project files, budgets and financial statements, motion picture film, videotapes, and audiotapes documenting projects and operations of Yale University Films. Records concerning the Yale Media Design Studio are also included.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Documentary films -- Production and direction; Audiotapes; Motion pictures (visual works); Videotapes; Yale University. Films; Yale University. Media Design Studio
- Art work for the cartoon, "Harold and Cynthia", Accession 1982-A-001
  - Art work for the cartoon, "Harold and Cynthia" (Box 1–2)
- Films and clips produced by University Public Information, circa 1978; Accession 1990-A-068
  Conditions Governing Access
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  - Language Proposal, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Robert Jeffers: Correspondence
    - 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Language Projects, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ohio State University: Robert Jeffers, 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - YaleUniversity: Media Design Studio, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Publicity forDeal(Film), undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Howard Sayre Weaver: Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Architectural History Foundation: Victoria Newhouse, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Howard Sayre Weaver: Phone Messages, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Mary Hunter Wolf Project, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Labov: Lerner Language Proposal, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Educational Films, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - American Regional Dialects Film, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Language Project: E. J. Vaughn and Jonathan Pearlman, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Language Project, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Language Project: Robert Jeffers, 1980, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Robert Freedman: Re: Language Project, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The Olmsted Legacy: Nightwork Sequence, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 24 - 28)
  - National Association for Olmsted Parks
    - 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Critiques forOlmsted: First Draft, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Critiques forOlmsted: First Draft, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Olmsted: II Correspondence and Notes
    - 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Olmsted Synopsis, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Olmsted Project: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Frederick Law Olmsted Project (Charles Capen McLaughlin)
    - 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - 1957-1979 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 48 - 50)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Olmsted Project, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities:OlmstedI: $48,841, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 54 - 55)
  - Olmsted Project
    - no date (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Local Programs, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - no date (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - no date (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - no date (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - no date (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - no date (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities:OlmstedDraft for 11/79 not submitted, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities:OlmstedDraft for 11/79 not submitted, undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities:Olmsted, February 18, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 65 - 66)
  - OlmstedOriginal, February 1980 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Sottnick Project: Exceptional People, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Proposals and Budgets (miscellaneous), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences Committee Materials, undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Kodaly, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Monitor Project, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Verbal Ape, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Olmsted Project, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Uses of the Humanities, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Herbert Brodkin: Titus Productions, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Yale: New Haven Educational Corporation, September 9, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Constitution: National Endowment for the Humanities Correspondence, February 10, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 80 - 82)
  - Constitution: National Endowment for the Humanities, June 1982 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - "A More Perfect Union": National Endowment for the Humanities, February 10, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - "A More Perfect Union": $57,269, July 10, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - "A More Perfect Union": $57,269, PN 20568, July 10, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Grant Application: Handicapped Media Services and Captioned Films Program, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 87 - 88)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting/Annenberg: Constitution, April 5, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 89 - 90)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Black West $988,022, GN 22193, January 30, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Piaget and Carousel Brochure - I, August 1982 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Piaget and Carousel Brochure - II, August 1982 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Grants and Contracts Office
    - 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - 1979 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: General, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: General, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: Public/Media Division I, 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: Public/Media Division II, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: Education Division, 1975-1983 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Van Gogh: Quotes I, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Van Gogh: Quotes II, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Van Gogh: Quotes III, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Van Gogh: Notes and Correspondence I, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Van Gogh: Notes and Correspondence II, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Van Gogh: Notes and Correspondence III, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Van Gogh: Notes and Correspondence IV, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Compassion, Henri Nouwen
    - I: Van Gogh Hold, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - II: Text for Recording, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - III: Text for Recording, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - IV: Text, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - V: Text, July 21, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - VI, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Cohen, Grossman and Zinkin, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Arthur Penn, undated (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Kubasik Packet, April 7, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - "Westering" Master and one Copy, undated (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Photos and Copies ofA Texas CowboyCover from Promotion of "Westering", undated (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Rockefeller Grant, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Rockefeller Correspondence, 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Rockefeller, 1977-1983 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Rockefeller, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Rockefeller Meeting Information, April 22, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Rockefeller, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Rockefeller, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Ford Foundation, 1973-1979 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Ford -Olmsted, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Ford Foundation, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Ford Foundation: Black Folklore Grant, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Ford Foundation: Black Folklore, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Ford Foundation: Vietnam, undated (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Ferris, William: Stills for Black Folklore, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Ferris, William, 1974-1979 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Inventory, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Kodaly, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Van Derzee Project I, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Van Derzee Project II, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Navajo Project: Screenplay, undated (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Navajo Project, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Navajo Project: Lionel Rogosin, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Roemer Letters, 1964-1974 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Faith Hubley, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting "Autobiography": Original, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting "After the Eye of the Storm", 1984 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting "Stalin", 1989 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting: "Orwell", 1983 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting: "Slavery", 1983 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Slavery and Antislavery InformationPN 20746, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Applications: "The Great Argument", 1982 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - "A More Perfect Union" Proposal, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Piaget Script, undated (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Piaget Contract, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Jean Piaget I, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Jean Piaget II, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Jean Piaget III, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Jean Piaget IV, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Jean Piaget V, 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Jean Piaget VI (miscellaneous), 1975-1981 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Jean Piaget: Distribution, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Lilly Foundation Endowment I: "Cattletown", 1976 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Lilly Endowment II, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Lilly Endowment III, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Lilly Endowment III, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Annual Reports of Lilly Endowment, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Guidance Association Film/Video, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - New HavenPiaget Screening, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Weisskopf, Victor, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Correspondence I: "Insights", 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Correspondence II: "Insights" Proposals, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - "Insights" Budget and Correspondence, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - "Insights" Notes, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Treasurer: EcklundComptrollers Office: Codlin, Turrotte, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Assistant Treasurer: Joel Wasserman, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Associate Treasurer: William J. Feeney, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Assistant Treasurer and Bursar: Nicoll, FrancisInsurance Manager: William Neale, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Media Design Studio, University Treasurer: Ecklund, John, 1974-1978 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Fanton, Jonathan: Campaign for Yale, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Provost: Hannah GrayLetter of Jan 14 to Sherry Penney, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Provost: Hannah GraySherry Penney (Space), 1980 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Penney File, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Provost: Abraham Goldstein, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Media Design Studio, University Provost Hannah Gray, 1965-1978 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Media Design Studio Budget Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Budget Work, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Boswell: Pittsburgh, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - BoswellProject, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Budget Work: Summary Statements, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Budget Work, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Budget Work, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - "Creation of a Character", 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - "Creation of a Character", 1976-1981 (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Media Design Studio Budget, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Rocky Express, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities:Olmsted, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Media Design Studio Budget, 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 200 - 201)
  - Cattletown Expenses, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Rockefeller, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Ford:OlmstedGrant, 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Ford: Olmsted Project, 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Media Design Studio, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: Proposal and Projections, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Budget Work, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Media Design Studio: General, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Media Design Studio: Remittance, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Statements and Substantiation, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 211 - 212)
  - Media Design Studio Budget, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 213 - 214)
  - Financial Ledger, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Budget, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Miscellaneous Copy/Printing, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Film Release With Fee, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - General, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Dan Distribution, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Butch Cassidy, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting/ASC Constitution, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting/Annenberg Correspondence Constitution, February 10, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Annenberg Correspondence Constitution, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 224 - 225)
  - George Orwell Project: Original Proposals, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 226)
  - Orwell Project: Apologies, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 227)
  - Orwell Project: Rejection, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 228)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: Orwell Application, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 229)
  - PeabodyMuseumCaptioning: Prints, Slides, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 230)
  - BoswellProject, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 231)
  - BoswellProject, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: London Journal GN 1651-80, Boswell Project, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 233)
  - Boswell: Final Report, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Quarterly Report forReid the Sheep Stealer, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Reid/BoswellProject: Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Reid Budgets, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - Reid Originals PN 0279, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - Reid Originals PN 0279, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - PTV: McGraw Hill Contract, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 241)
  - Harris-McGraw Rights, Aleinikoff, 1974-1981 (Box 7, Folder 242)
  - Booker Correspondence, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - Heinemann - Reid, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - BBC Script: Reid, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - BBC Film Schedule: Reid, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - Prints from BBC Reid, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Mark Harris Screenplay: "It Looked Like For Ever", 1979 (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - BoswellScreening Publicity, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - Reid Production Plan, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - BoswellScreening: New Haven, April 29, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - 2ndBoswellScreening, November 9, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - Boswell: Private Papers, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - Boswell: New York Screening, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - BoswellReviews, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Mark Harris, 1977-1983 (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - BoswellCorrespondence: University of Pittsburgh, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - BoswellFile: University of Pittsburgh
    - 1981 (Box 7, Folder 258)
    - 1980 (Box 7, Folder 259)
    - 1979 (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Boswell: Pittsburgh Grant, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 261)
  - Memo to Executive Committee Re: Status of Media Design Studio: I, April 30, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 262)
  - Memo to Executive Committee Re: Status of Media Design Studio: II, April 30, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 263)
  - Lowenthal: Hiss case, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 264)
  - First Amendment I, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - First Amendment II, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 266)
  - Film:Harold and Cynthia, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Van Gogh Tapes, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - YaleUniversityPress, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 269)
  - Images, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 270)
  - OlmstedOriginal, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 271)
  - Olmsted, undated (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Museum Tour Captioning for the Hearing Impaired, Original, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Media Aids for Handicapped: J. M. Foundation, undated (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Museum Captions, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Learning Disabilities Experience, Original, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - "Westering", 1977 (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Sottnick, Mark, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Project Proposals: Monitor and Merrimack, 1968-1980 (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - Monitor-Merrimack Project, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - Monitor-Merrimack Project, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - IATSE (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - Screen Actors Guild West, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - Screen Actors Guild, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 285)
  - Screen Actors Guild Television Agreement, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - Directors Guild (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 287)
  - Writers Guild, 1976-1988 (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - Writers Guild West, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 289)
  - The Film Fund, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 290)
  - Vendors G-P
    - Norac Productions, undated (Box 8, Folder 291)
    - Motion Pictures Enterprises, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 292)
    - Pan Am, undated (Box 8, Folder 293)
    - Pitney Bowes, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 294)
    - Plastic Reel Corporation, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 295)
    - Producers' Sound Service, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 296)
    - Postal Service, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 297)
    - Pyramid, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 298)
  - BoswellSupplemental Original, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - Pyramid Films: Carousel, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - The Life and Times of Huey P. Long, undated (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - Screening Rooms, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 302)
  - Kitchen Renovations, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 303)
  - Retype of Stalin (project), undated (Box 8, Folder 304)
  - Stalin: Treatment/ChronologyDrafts and Comments, undated (Box 8, Folder 305)
  - Stalin: Revisions, undated (Box 9, Folder 306)
  - George Orwell: A Backward Glance, 1984-1903, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 307 - 309)
  - University News Bureau: Stephen Kezerian, 1969-1976 (Box 9, Folder 310)
  - Westering, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 311)
  - Boswell for the Defence, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 312)
  - PiagetNegatives, undated (Box 9, Folder 313)
  - PiagetSlides, undated (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - PiagetPictures, undated (Box 9, Folder 315)
  - Westering, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 316)
  - The Chronicle of Higher Education:Article on Yale Film, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 317)
  - Publicity about Film Program: Pilot Program, 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - Publicity about Film Programs: John and Faith Hubley, 1946-1977 (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - Publicity: Death of John Hubley, 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 320)
  - Westering(?): Photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder 321)
  - Publicity: Newspapers, 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 322)
  - Publicity: Miscellaneous, 1960-1976 (Box 9, Folder 323)
  - List of Films and Cassettes to Archives, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 324)
  - Boswell for the Defence, undated (Box 9, Folder 325)
  - Boswell for the Defence: Photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder 326)
  - Publications about Media Design Studio And Yale University Films, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 327)
  - BoswellPublicity and Reviews, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 328)
  - Howard Sayre Weaver, 1964-1980 (Box 9, Folder 329)
  - Executive Committee of Media Design Studio, 1977-1981 (Box 9, Folder 330)
  - Termination: Media Design Studio, Yale University Films Notes / Correpondence / Minutes of Executive Committee, 1983-1989 (Box 9, Folder 331)
  - Media Design Studio, Yale University Films: Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 332)
  - Media Design Studio: Henry Chauncey Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 333)
  - Media Design Studio, Yale University Films: Annual Report to Secretary, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 334)
  - Articles about Media Design Studio, 1975-1982 (Box 9, Folder 335)
  - Media Design Studio Relationship to Yale, undated (Box 9, Folder 336)
  - Procedures for Exercising the Responsibilities of the Yale University Media Design Studio, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 337)
  - Internal Memorandum, September 11, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 338)
  - YaleDaily NewsMagazine ArticleRe: Media Design Studio/Howard Sayre Weaver, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 339)
  - IWAPP: Award forPiaget on Piaget, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 340)
  - American Film Festival: Piaget IWAPP Award, Certificate of Honor for Piaget, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 341)
  - San FranciscoInternational Film FestivalThe Resurrectionists, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 342)
  - Superfest XII Local 34Commendation Award forStranger in a Family, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 343)
  - Cine Award:Give My Poor Heart Ease, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 344)
  - Cine Award:To Be A Man, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 345)
  - Prints from BBCBoswell, undated (Box 10, Folder 346)
  - Personnel, undated (Box 11, Folder 347)
  - Slavery and Antislavery
    - A 44713 PN 20746, July-December 1982 (Box 11, Folder 348)
    - 896A-53-44713: Notes and Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 349)
    - Budget and Analysis, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 350)
    - Bills and Requisitions, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 351)
  - Endowment Fund: Statements896A-53-25575, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 352)
  - "A More Perfect Union" Constitution Project (old)PN 20568, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 353)
  - Old Constitution: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 354)
  - "Carousel" Correspondence, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 355)
  - Media Design Studio: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 356)
  - Butch Cassidy Statements, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 357)
  - Lilly Foundation (Van Gogh)
    - 896B-53-57069 not cleared, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 358)
    - 896B-53-57069 cleared, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 359)
    - 896B-53-57069 Statements, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 360)
    - 896B-53-57069 Cleared Earlier, 1978-1982 (Box 11, Folder 361)
  - American Dances (lacking), undated (Box 11, Folder 362)
  - American Bar Association, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 363)
  - Amish-Larrimore and Taylor, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 364)
  - Alper Project, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 365)
  - Autobiography (lacking), undated (Box 11, Folder 366)
    - Budgets
    - Annual, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 367)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 368)
    - Salary Changes, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 369)
    - Status Reports for Funding, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 370)
  - Beauty:The Eye of the Beholder, undated (Box 11, Folder 371)
  - Bernett, Hugh, Davies, Ty Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 372)